https://www.echristianpr.com/website-terms-of-use-and-privacy-policy

1.         User’s Acknowledgment and Acceptance of Terms
ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC, a Texas limited liability company (or any successor entity) (referred to as “us” or “we”) provides the www.echristianpr.com website and various related services (together referred to as this “website”) subject to your compliance with all the terms, conditions, and notices contained or referenced herein (these “Terms of Use”), as well as any other written agreement between us (or your company).  In addition, when using particular services or materials on this website, users shall be subject to any posted guidelines or rules applicable to such services or materials that may contain terms and conditions in addition to those in these Terms of Use.  All such guidelines or rules are hereby incorporated by reference into these Terms of Use.
BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE.  IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THE THESE TERMS OF USE, PLEASE EXIT THE WEBSITE NOW.  YOUR REMEDY FOR DISSATISFACTION WITH THIS WEBSITE, OR ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, CONTENT, OR OTHER INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH THIS WEBSITE, IS TO STOP USING THE WEBSITE.  YOUR AGREEMENT WITH US REGARDING COMPLIANCE WITH THESE TERMS OF USE BECOMES EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON COMMENCEMENT OF YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE.
These Terms of Use are effective as of August 1, 2014.  We reserve the right to change these Terms of Use from time to time without notice to you.  You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this website and these Terms of Use periodically and to be aware of any modifications.  Your continued use of this website after such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified Terms of Use and agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Terms of Use.
THIS WEBSITE IS FOR GENERAL INFORMATION ONLY.  THE INFORMATION PRESENTED DOES NOT CONSTITUTE SPECIFIC OR INDIVIDUAL ADVICE OR COUNSEL, AND YOUR USE OF IT DOES NOT CREATE A PROFESSIONAL RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN YOU AND US.  NO VISITOR TO THIS WEBSITE SHOULD ACT ON THE BASIS OF ANY CONTENT INCLUDED HEREIN WITHOUT SEEKING THE APPROPRIATE PROFESSIONAL COUNSEL FROM A PROFESSIONAL THEY HAVE FORMALLY ENGAGED.  ANY CASE STUDIES, TESTIMONIALS, OR OTHER EXAMPLES ON THIS WEBSITE DO NOT GUARANTEE A SIMILAR OUTCOME.  THE CONTENTS OF THIS WEBSITE DO NOT CONSTITUTE PROFESSIONAL ADVICE AND YOU MAY NOT RELY ON THE CONTENTS OF THIS WEBSITE AS SUCH.
As used in these Terms of Use, references to our “Affiliates” include our owners, subsidiaries, affiliated companies, officers, directors, suppliers, partners, sponsors, and advertisers, and includes (without limitation) all parties involved in creating, producing, and/or delivering this website and/or its contents.
2.         Use of Website
You are solely responsible for providing, at your own expense, all equipment necessary to use this website, including a computer, modem, and your own Internet access (including payment of telephone or other service fees associated with such access).
We reserve the sole right to either modify or discontinue the website, including any features therein, at any time with or without notice to you.  We shall not be liable to you or any third party should we exercise such right.
You understand and agree that temporary interruptions in this website may occur as normal events.  You further understand and agree that we have no control over third party networks you may access in the course of the use of this website, and therefore, delays and disruption of other network transmissions are completely beyond our control.
You understand and agree that this website is provided “AS IS” and that we assume no responsibility for the timeliness, deletion, mis?delivery or failure to store any user communications or personalization settings.
You also grant us the right to disclose to third parties any data you may transmit to us via the website or otherwise.  The information we obtain through your use of this website is subject to our Privacy Policy, which is specifically incorporated by reference into these Terms of Use.
3.         Conduct on Website
Your use of the website is subject to all applicable laws and regulations, including Netiquette, and you are solely responsible for the contents of your communications through the website.  By posting information in or otherwise using any communications service, chat room, message board, newsgroup, software library, or other service, if any, that may be available to you on or through this website, you agree that you will not upload, share, post, or otherwise distribute or facilitate distribution of any content ?? including text, communications, software, images, sounds, data, or other information ?? that:
(a)  Is unlawful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, libelous, deceptive, fraudulent, invasive of another’s privacy, tortious, contains descriptions or accounts of sexual acts (including but not limited to sexual language of a violent or threatening nature directed at another individual or group of individuals), or otherwise violates our rules or policies;
(b)  Victimizes, harasses, degrades, or intimidates an individual or group of individuals on the basis of religion, gender, sexual orientation, race, ethnicity, age, or disability;
(c)  Infringes on any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright, right of publicity, or other proprietary right of any party;
(d)  Constitutes unauthorized or unsolicited advertising, junk or bulk e-mail (also known as “spamming”), chain letters, any other form of unauthorized solicitation, or any form of lottery or gambling;
(e)  Contains software viruses or any other computer code, files, or programs that are designed or intended to disrupt, damage, or limit the functioning of any software, hardware, or telecommunications equipment or to damage or obtain unauthorized access to any data or other information of any third party; or
(f)   Impersonates any person or entity, including any of our employees or representatives.
We neither endorse nor assume any liability for the contents of any material uploaded or submitted by third party users of the website.  We generally do not pre?screen, monitor, or edit the content posted by users of communications services, chat rooms, message boards, newsgroups, software libraries, or other interactive services, if any, that may be available on or through this website.  However, we and our agents have the right at their sole discretion to remove any content that, in our judgment, does not comply with these Terms of Use and any other rules of user conduct for our website, or is otherwise harmful, objectionable, or inaccurate.  We are not responsible for any failure or delay in removing such content.  You hereby consent to such removal and waive any claim against us arising out of such removal of content.
In addition, not all areas of the website may be available to you or other authorized users of the website.  You shall not interfere with anyone else’s use and enjoyment of the website.  Users who violate systems or network security may incur criminal or civil liability.
You agree that we may at any time, and at our sole discretion, terminate your access to the website without prior notice to you for violating any of the above provisions.  In addition, you acknowledge that we will cooperate fully with investigations of violations of systems or network security at other websites, including cooperating with law enforcement authorities in investigating suspected criminal violations.
4.         Third Party Websites and Information
This website may link you to other websites on the Internet or otherwise include references to information, documents, software, materials and/or services provided by other parties.  These websites may contain information or material that some people may find inappropriate or offensive.  These other websites and parties are not under our control, and you acknowledge that we are not responsible for the accuracy, copyright compliance, legality, decency, or any other aspect of the content of such websites, nor are we responsible for errors or omissions in any references to other parties or their products and services, including but not limited to any virus, malware, or other harmful software.  The inclusion of such a link or reference is provided merely as a convenience and does not imply endorsement of, or association with, the website or party by us, or any warranty of any kind, either express or implied.
5.         Intellectual Property Information
All content on this website is Copyright © 2014 ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC All Rights Reserved.
For purposes of these Terms of Use, “content” is defined as any information, communications, software, photos, video, graphics, music, sounds, and other material and services that can be viewed by users on our website.  This includes, but is in no way limited to, message boards, blogs, chat, and other original content.
By accepting these Terms of Use, you acknowledge and agree that all content presented to you on this website is protected by copyrights, trademarks, service marks, patents or other proprietary rights and laws, and, except as may be otherwise set forth in any license or other similar agreement between us and third parties for the display of content on the website, is the sole property of ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC and/or its Affiliates.  You are only permitted to use the content as expressly authorized by us or the specific content provider.  Except for a single copy made for personal use only, you may not copy, reproduce, modify, republish, upload, post, transmit, or distribute any documents or information from this website in any form or by any means without prior written permission from us or the specific content provider, and you are solely responsible for obtaining permission before reusing any copyrighted material that is available on this website.  Any unauthorized use of the materials appearing on this website may violate copyright, trademark and other applicable laws and could result in criminal or civil penalties.  Neither we nor our Affiliates warrant or represent that your use of materials displayed on, or obtained through, this website will not infringe the rights of third parties.
The following are representative registered trademarks, trademarks or service marks of ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC or its Affiliates:
All custom graphics, icons, logos and service names are registered trademarks, trademarks or service marks of ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC or its Affiliates.  All other trademarks or service marks are property of their respective owners.  Nothing in these Terms of Use grants you any right to use any trademark, service mark, logo, and/or the name of ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC or its Affiliates.
Certain of the ideas, software and processes incorporated into the website design and hosting service that is available on this website are protected by patent applications pending in the United States, and we intend to prepare and file additional patent applications in selected foreign jurisdictions.
6.         User’s Materials
Subject to our Privacy Policy, any communication or material that you transmit to this website or to us, whether by electronic mail or other means, for any reason, will be treated as non?confidential and non?proprietary.  While you retain all rights in such communications or material, you grant us and our designated licensees a non?exclusive, paid?up, perpetual, and worldwide right to copy, distribute, display, perform, publish, translate, adapt, modify, and otherwise use such material for any purpose regardless of the form or medium (now known or not currently known) in which it is used.
Please do not submit confidential or proprietary information to us unless we have mutually agreed in writing otherwise.  We are also unable to accept your unsolicited ideas or proposals, so please do not submit them to us in any circumstance.  Electronic mail or other communications to us through this website are not secure.  Accordingly, we do not guarantee the confidentiality of such communications.
We respect the intellectual property of others, and we ask you to do the same.  If you or any user of this website believes its copyright, trademark or other property rights have been infringed by a posting on this website, you or the user should send notification to our Designated Agent (as identified below) immediately.  To be effective, the notification must include:
(a)  A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed’
(b)  Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed;
(c)  Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact the complaining party, such as address, telephone number and, if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted;
(d)  Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be subject to infringing activity and that is to be removed and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the materials.
(e)  A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, agent, or the law; and
(f)   A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringing.
Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. Sec. 512(c), our Designated Agent for Notice of claims of copyright infringement can be reached as indicated below.
Designated Agent for Claimed Infringement:
ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC
Attn:  General Counsel, Leffingwell Law, P.C.
Attn:  Frank Leffingwell
211 W. Bagdad Avenue
Round Rock, Texas 78667
Your acknowledge and agree that upon receipt of a notice of a claim of copyright infringement, we may immediately remove the identified materials from our website without liability to you or any other party and that the claims of the complaining party and the party that originally posted the materials will be referred to the United States Copyright Office for adjudication as provided in the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.
7.         Disclaimer of Warranties
ALL CONTENT ON THIS WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR THE WARRANTY OF NON?INFRINGEMENT.  WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, WE MAKE NO WARRANTY THAT (a) THE CONTENT WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, (b) THE CONTENT WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR?FREE, (c) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE CONTENTS WILL BE EFFECTIVE, ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, OR (d) THE QUALITY OF ANY CONTENT OR INFORMATION OBTAINED BY YOU FROM THE WEBSITE FROM US OR OUR AFFILIATES WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS OR BE FREE FROM MISTAKES, ERRORS OR DEFECTS.
THIS WEBSITE COULD INCLUDE TECHNICAL OR OTHER MISTAKES, INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS.  WE MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THE CONTENT AT THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING THE PRICES AND DESCRIPTIONS OF ANY PRODUCTS LISTED HEREIN, AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.  THE CONTENT AT THIS WEBSITE MAY BE OUT OF DATE, AND WE MAKE NO COMMITMENT TO UPDATE SUCH CONTENT.
THE USE OF THE WEBSITE OR THE DOWNLOADING OR OTHER ACQUISITION OF ANY MATERIALS THROUGH THIS WEBSITE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND WITH YOUR AGREEMENT THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM SUCH ACTIVITIES.
Through your use of the website, you may have the opportunities to engage in commercial transactions with other users and vendors.  You acknowledge that all transactions relating to any merchandise or services offered by any party, including, but not limited to the purchase terms, payment terms, warranties, guarantees, maintenance and delivery terms relating to such transactions, are agreed to solely between the seller or purchaser of such merchandise and services and you.  WE MAKE NO WARRANTY REGARDING ANY TRANSACTIONS EXECUTED THROUGH, OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS WEBSITE, AND YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT SUCH TRANSACTIONS ARE CONDUCTED ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK.  ANY WARRANTY THAT IS PROVIDED IN CONNECTION WITH ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, MATERIALS, OR INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH THIS WEBSITE FROM A THIRD PARTY IS PROVIDED SOLELY BY SUCH THIRD PARTY, AND NOT BY US OR ANY OTHER OF OUR AFFILIATES.
Content available through this website often represents the opinions and judgments of an information provider, website user, or other person or entity not connected with ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC.  We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy or reliability of, any opinion, advice, or statement made by anyone other than an authorized ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC spokesperson speaking in his/her official capacity.  Please refer to the specific editorial policies, if any, posted on various sections of this website for further information, which policies are incorporated by reference into these Terms of Use.
In addition, the materials on this website may include sample or form agreements, letters or other documents, including financially or legally significant documents such as contracts and other items (“Forms“).  These Forms are provided solely as examples of typical documents of their kind, and the delivery and use of Forms does not constitute legal, accounting or other professional advice.  Under no circumstances will ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC or its Affiliates be liable for any loss or damages caused by your reliance on information or advice obtained through this website, including your use of any of the Forms.  It is your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, opinions, advice, Forms or other content available on or through this website.  In particular, you are urged to consult an appropriate professional licensed in your jurisdiction before using any Forms or otherwise relying on any legal, accounting, or other professional advice or information obtained on or through this website.
SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES, SO SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
8.         Limitation of Liability
Your exclusive remedy and our entire liability, if any, for any claims arising out of these Terms of Use and your use of this website shall be limited to the amount you paid us for access to the website during the six (6) month period before the act giving rise to the liability.
IN NO EVENT SHALL WE OR OUR AFFILIATES BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE OR OF ANY WEB WEBSITE REFERENCED OR LINKED TO FROM THIS WEBSITE.
FURTHER, WE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE IN ANY WAY FOR THIRD PARTY GOODS AND SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH THIS WEBSITE OR FOR ASSISTANCE IN CONDUCTING COMMERCIAL TRANSACTIONS THROUGH THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE PROCESSING OF ORDERS.
SOME JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
9.         Indemnification
Upon a request by us, you agree to defend, indemnify, and hold us and our Affiliates harmless from all liabilities, claims, and expenses, including attorney’s fees, that arise from your use or misuse of this website.  We reserve the right, at our own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will cooperate with us in asserting any available defenses.
10.       Participation in Promotion
From time to time, this website may include advertisements offered by third parties.  You may enter into correspondence with or participate in promotions of the advertisers showing their products on this website.  Any such correspondence or promotions, including the delivery of and the payment for goods and services, and any other terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such correspondence or promotions, are solely between you and the advertiser.  We assume no liability, obligation or responsibility for any part of any such correspondence or promotion.
11.       International Use
Although this website may be accessible worldwide, we make no representation that materials on this website are appropriate or available for use in locations outside the United States, and accessing them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited.  Those who choose to access this website from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.  Any offer for any product, service, and/or information made in connection with this website is void where prohibited.
12.       Termination of Use
You agree that we may, in our sole discretion, terminate or suspend your access to all or part of the website with or without notice and for any reason, including, without limitation, breach of these Terms of Use.  Any suspected fraudulent, abusive or illegal activity may be grounds for terminating your relationship and may be referred to appropriate law enforcement authorities.
Upon termination or suspension, regardless of the reasons therefore, your right to use the services available on this website immediately ceases, and you acknowledge and agree that we may immediately deactivate or delete your account and all related information and files in your account and/or bar any further access to such files or this website.  We shall not be liable to you or any third party for any claims or damages arising out of any termination or suspension or any other actions taken by us in connection therewith.  All sections of these Terms of Use, as well as your liability for any unpaid fees, shall survive any termination.
13.       Governing Law
This website (excluding any linked websites) is controlled by us from our offices within the State of Texas, United States of America.  It can be accessed from all 50 states, as well as from other countries around the world.  As each of these places has laws that may differ from those of Texas, by accessing this website both of us agree that the statutes and laws of the State of Texas, without regard to the conflicts of laws principles thereof.  Each of us agrees and hereby submits to the exclusive personal jurisdiction and venue of the Courts of Travis County and the United States District Court for the Western District of Texas with respect to such matters.
14.       Notices
All notices to a party shall be in writing and shall be made either via e-mail or conventional mail.  Notices to us must be sent to the attention of Customer Service at info@echristianpr.com, if by e-mail, or at ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC, 823 Congress Avenue, Suite 1505, Austin, Texas 78701-2457, if by conventional mail.  In addition, we may broadcast notices or messages through the website to inform you of changes to the website or other matters of importance, and such broadcasts shall constitute notice to you.
Any notices or communication under these Terms of Use will be deemed delivered to the party receiving such communication (a) on the delivery date if delivered personally to the party; (b) two business days after deposit with a commercial overnight carrier, with written verification of receipt; (c) five business days after the mailing date, if sent by US mail, return receipt requested; (d) on the delivery date if transmitted by confirmed facsimile; or (e) on the delivery date if transmitted by confirmed e-mail.
15.       Entire Agreement
These terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement and understanding between us concerning the subject matter hereof and supersedes all prior agreements and understandings of the parties with respect thereto.  These Terms of Use may NOT be altered, supplemented, or amended by the use of any other document(s).  Any attempt to alter, supplement or amend this document or to enter an order for products or services which are subject to additional or altered terms and conditions shall be null and void, unless otherwise agreed to in a written agreement signed by you and us.  To the extent that anything in or associated with this website is in conflict or inconsistent with these Terms of Use, these Terms of Use shall take precedence.
16.       Miscellaneous
In any action to enforce these Terms of Use, the prevailing party will be entitled to costs and attorneys’ fees.  Any cause of action brought by you against us or our Affiliates must be instituted with one year after the cause of action arises or be deemed forever waived and barred.
You may not assign your rights and obligations under these Terms of Use, and any purported attempt to do so shall be null and void.  We may free assign our rights and obligations under these Terms of Use.
You agree not to sell, resell, reproduce, duplicate, copy or use for any commercial purposes any portion of this website, or use of or access to this website.
In addition to any excuse provided by applicable law, we shall be excused from liability for non?delivery or delay in delivery of products and services available through our website arising from any event beyond our reasonable control, whether or not foreseeable by either party, including but not limited to, labor disturbance, war, fire, accident, adverse weather, inability to secure transportation, governmental act or regulation, and other causes or events beyond our reasonable control, whether or not similar to those which are enumerated above.
If any part of these Terms of Use is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.
Any failure by us to enforce or exercise any provision of these Terms of Use or related rights shall not constitute a waiver of that right or provision.
17.       Contact Information
Except as explicitly noted on this website, the services described by this website are offered by ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC, a Texas limited liability company, located at 8008 Spicewood Lane, Austin, TX 78759.  Any such services would only be provided pursuant to a fully executed engagement agreement in a form acceptable to us. Our telephone number is (512) 472-9599.  If you are a United States resident, you may have this same information e-mailed to you by sending a letter to the foregoing address with your e-mail address and a request for this information.  If you notice that any user is violating these Terms of Use, please contact us at info@echristianpr.com.
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY When accessing our website(s), ELIZABETH CHRISTIAN PUBLIC RELATIONS LLC, a Texas limited liability company (“ECPR”) will collect and learn certain information about you during your visit. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when visiting our site. If you visit our site to read or download information on our pages, we collect and store certain information about you including but not limited to: 1. The name of the domain from which you access the Internet; 2. The date and time you access our site; 3. The Internet address of the website you used to link directly to our site; 4. The geographic region, including but not limited to, the zip code from which you have accessed the ECPR website; and 5. The unique device identifier for the device on which you have accessed the ECPR website, including the information which may be derived from such identifier. If you identify yourself to ECPR, including sending us an e-mail, or if you otherwise transmit information to us containing your personal information, EPCR may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with EPCR, you may not opt out of receiving these communications. We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve EPCR’s products, services, advertising, and customer communications. If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs. EPCR’s website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. EPCR treats information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. At times EPCR may make certain of your personal information available to strategic partners that work with EPCR in order to provide products and services, or that help EPCR market its products and services to customers. Personal information will only be shared by EPCR to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for such third parties’ marketing purposes. EPCR may also share personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever EPCR operates. It may be necessary ? by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence ? for EPCR to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party. EPCR websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties. If you have any questions or concerns about EPCR’s Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us. EPCR may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are responsible for reviewing this policy from time to time to familiarize yourself with any updates, revisions, or modifications to this Privacy Policy.
Find out how we can help you build your business.
© 2020					Elizabeth Christian Public Relations. All Rights Reserved. •
Website Terms of Service and Privacy Policy
•
An Alter Endeavors Site.
